[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was Captain James T. Kirks first mate on the USS Enterprise NCC-1701?", "correct_answer": "Mr. Spock", "incorrect_answers": ["Montgomery Scotty Scott", "Dr. Leonard Bones McCoy", "Hikaru Sulu"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Phantom of the Opera, Raoul remembers Christine, while listening to which song?", "correct_answer": "Think of Me", "incorrect_answers": ["Magical Lasso", "The Mirror", "All I Ask of You"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of insect is the smallest known insect on the planet?", "correct_answer": "Wasp", "incorrect_answers": ["Cockroach", "Ant", "Fly"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor, whose autobiography was called My Wicked Wicked Ways, starred in the movies Adventures of Robin Hood (1938), Istanbul (1957) and They Died with Their Boots On (1941).", "correct_answer": "Errol Flynn", "incorrect_answers": ["Claude Rains", "Anthony Quinn", "George Reeves"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The term albino comes from the Latin word albus.  An albino person or animal is characterised by what?", "correct_answer": "A lack of pigmentation in the skin, eyes and hair", "incorrect_answers": ["Extremely dark pigmentation of the skin", "Redness of the skin", "Oily skin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the actual name of the hotel where parts of the above mentioned film was shot?", "correct_answer": "Amargosa Hotel and Opera House", "incorrect_answers": ["Indian Springs Inn", "Baghdad Inn", "Longstreet Hotel, Resort and Casino"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these famous buildings is located on the Quai dOrsay, in Paris?", "correct_answer": "The French Ministry of Foreign Affairs", "incorrect_answers": ["The Tomb of Napoleon", "The Picasso Museum of Paris", "The Eiffel Tower"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This film, directed by Alfred Jackson, was released by Disney on December 21, 1937 and featured Billy Gilbert as Sneezy.", "correct_answer": "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", "incorrect_answers": ["Song of the South", "Rose Red and Rose White", "Gullivers Travels"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Male turkeys are monogamous and will stay with one female for life.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This film which opened on June 6th, 2006 is a remake of the 1976 British film of the same name.", "correct_answer": "The Omen", "incorrect_answers": ["Pulse", "The Haunting", "The Amityville Horror"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Earth orbits the Sun at an average distance of how many million miles?", "correct_answer": "93", "incorrect_answers": ["42", "89", "101"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played Mrs. Powers, the music teacher, in the movie Lean on Me?", "correct_answer": "Sandra Reaves-Phillips", "incorrect_answers": ["Della Reese", "Halle Berry", "Loretta Divine"]}]